* .

Menu

* .

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

Our privacy policy is written to help you to understand how VIBE CYBER LLC (VIBEcyber) handles “Personally identifiable information” (PII). PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website and apps.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website or apps?**
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Like most websites, vibecyber.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Vibecyber.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use our website. From time to time, vibecyber.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our website.

Vibecyber.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Vibecyber.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information to third parties unless legally obliged to do so.

When registering or submitting a form on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details. See below on what happens with that data.

**When do we collect information?**
-----------------------------------

#### On our website:

We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site.

#### Nextcloud Apps and Files

Our apps only communicate with your own Nextcloud server and do not send any data to us. The Play Store version of Nextcloud apps equal to or newer than 1.5.0 for Nextcloud, supports push notifications which use the Google servers. However, Google does not have access to the actual notification data. Only a header with a subject is sent via Google, and in encrypted form, and the rest of the content is retrieved directly from your Nextcloud server and **not** sent through Google. The iOS client works in a similar way.

**How do we use your information?**
-----------------------------------

We may use the information we collect from our web site visitors in the following ways:

* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* If you supply us with an email address, to send periodic emails regarding your interest in our technology, and to follow up after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries).

**How do we protect visitor information?**
------------------------------------------

We only collect names and email addresses from visitors who request access to a whitepaper, and from registered users of our apps.

We may use Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Transport Layer Security (TLS) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information, to maintain the safety of personal information.

**Do we use “cookies”?**
------------------------

We do not use any cookies on our web site.

In the VIBE enabled Nextcloud environment, we only use cookies on our Web Administration Management Console (WMC) for two purposes:

1. Administrator authentication check, and logging of Admin access.
2. For improving the user experience (browser related information). In all cases no user-related data or privacy relevant data is stored. And no username or password are captured or cached.

**Third-party disclosure**
--------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Think aggregated statistics (number of website visitors in a particular month) or trends (e.g. We see an increase in the number of visitors from a particular country, or region).

**Third-party links**
---------------------

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**Contact**
-----------

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at privacy@vibecyber.com

**Privacy Policy Changes**
--------------------------

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and at our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Governing Law**
-----------------

These terms and conditions, and all matters relating directly or indirectly to this Site and our apps shall be construed, interpreted, applied and governed in all respects in accordance with the laws of the United States of America, without regard to its conflicts or choice of law provisions.

**For any inquiry, feedback or complaint please contact:**

VIBE CYBER LLC  
1124 Sylvan Dr  
Sarasota FL-34234, United States of America

Email: privacy@vibecyber.com

All product names and trademarks are the property of their respective owners, which might in no way be associated or affiliated with VIBE.

Last Edited on July 13, 2024

VIBE CYBER LLC  
1124 Sylvan Dr, Sarasota FL-34234, United States of America

Menu

Andrew Parlock
--------------

#### Advisor

Andrew is a senior executive with extensive background in Applications Engineering, and in particular, Business Development. With an MBA, and an undergrad degree in Aerospace (aka “rocket science”), and having realized high-level security clearance with the US Government, Andrew is a subject-matter expert when it comes to helping our team navigate the complex world of government and its related businesses and agencies. In Andrew’s words, he “thrives in the chaos of the unknown where so many opportunities exist.”

Andrew is a senior executive with extensive background in Applications Engineering, and in particular, Business Development. With an MBA, and an undergrad degree in Aerospace (aka “rocket science”), and having realized high-level security clearance with the US Government, Andrew is a subject-matter expert when it comes to helping our team navigate the complex world of government and its related businesses and agencies. In Andrew’s words, he “thrives in the chaos of the unknown where so many opportunities exist.”

Chuck Brooks
------------

#### Advisor

Named Top Person To Follow on Tech by LinkedIn. Former Technology Partner Advisor at Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation. Helped “stand up” Office of Legislative at DHS. Served as first Director of Legislative Affairs at the DHS Science & Technology Directorate. A thought leader, influencer, technology evangelist. A featured writer/speaker/blogger. Topics include: homeland security, cyber security, CBRNE, artificial intelligence (AI), Internet of Things (IoT), science & technology, public/private partnerships, risk management, blockchain, innovation. Published in FORBES, Huffington Post, InformationWeek, MIT Sloan Blog, Computerworld, Federal Times, NextGov and many more.

Olivier Rouit
-------------

#### Senior Embedded Security Architect

Formerly educated with a degree in Applied Electronics Engineering and Industrial Computer Science from ENSEA, France, and in Artificial Intelligence from the renowned ENSIMAG University in Grenoble. France, Olivier’s first significant role in Applied Research was with Gemplus’s Telecom Division. An expert in embedded security, Olivier has worked extensively on numerous research projects ranging from the first implementation of an EAP SIM, in collaboration with CISCO, to the first implementation of a Javacard OTP with Verisign. Recognized as an expert in identity-management embedded technology, Olivier is an award-winning engineer who today is leading embedded development projects for VIBE.

Heiko Vetkamp
-------------

#### Advisor

Heiko worked at Philips for 13.5 years in several European countries, and he worked at Halo Creative & Design Ltd. at its headquarters in Hong Kong and Operations in China & US.  Heiko is a co-founder of [Purive](https://purive.com/about-purive/what-makes-us-different).  Heiko is a practical, professional manager with a proven track record in Supply Chain, Customer service, Planning & Logistics, Key account and Sales Management, General Management and Change Management.  Being a Certified Lean Six Sigma Black Belt, Heiko has experience in leading complex multi-site international supply chain projects, customer service & logistics management, the building and managing of intensive partnerships on several levels for international key accounts and distributors, the building of effective sales organisations, profit & loss responsibility, business development, and large integration and change management projects.

Heiko has a Master of Science (MSc) in Industrial Engineering from the Georgia Institute of Technology, in Atlanta with a focus on Economic decision analysis, and a Master of Science (MSc) in Mechanical engineering from the University of Twente in the Netherlands with a focus on Production and Operations management.  Today Heiko lives in Netherlands.  Heiko speaks Dutch, English, and German.

Craig Stark
-----------

#### Advisor

Craig Stark has over 30 years of Business Development experience with new technologies and bringing complex solutions to market from large to start-up sized companies. With deep experience in strategic partnerships, channel development, solution marketing, product and industry marketing, Craig uses an agile, collaborative approach of innovation management to build sustaining value for partners and clients. Craig has focused on IoT and transformative technologies for the past five years. His current work with Strategy of Things focuses on Smart Systems, Smart Buildings, and Platform Business Models. Prior to that, he spent six years in the smart systems development business, where he served as CTO and co-lead in design authority at Blackstone Gates, an international CX and loyalty strategy consultancy. Craig has served on the CIO Strategy Council (Data and Security Standards), The Conference Board of Canada (advisory on IP strategy) and as an industry partner for the Innovation, Science and Economic Development for the National IP Strategy council and currently supports the NSERC National IoT Research Chair in support of bridging applied research to several industry segments. Craig has supported research efforts for the US NIST IoT Infrastructure investment project to apply to several industry and vendor segments.

Paul Hager
----------

#### Advisor

Paul has extensive experience in cybersecurity. He served as the U.S. Representative to NATO for Information Security. As Special Assistant to the Director of the NSA he participated in technology research, investment, and partnerships in international cybersecurity and telecom technologies. Early in his NSA career, he carried out system penetration testing (hacking), and was an early team member of the first U.S. National Computer Security Center. Paul has authored national and international policies and publications/books on information security. Paul earned his M.B.A. in Corporate Finance from the University of Pennsylvania Wharton School of Business, and a Master of Public Administration (MPA) in International Policy, from Harvard University. His undergraduate degrees are from the University of North Carolina, a B.S. in Mathematics and a B.A. with Honors in Psychology.

Bob Bergman
-----------

#### Standards Strategy

A total of 50 years of experience in software engineering, Decision Sciences, System Dynamics Modeling, Scenario Planning, International Standards, business strategy synthesis, and simulation. Bob’s background includes 12 years of flight simulator design for USAF high-performance aircraft and 28 years at Intel applying quantitative decision methodologies to improve international standards negotiations and strategic business decisions. Bob represented Intel at GSM Association, 3GPP (wireless com standards), IETF, oneM2m (IOT standards), and Open Mobile Alliance (Digital Rights Management standards). Bob attended MIT and SUNY at Albany earning a BS degree in Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, with graduate work in system dynamics.

Dr. William “Dollar” Young, Jr
------------------------------

#### Advisor

Dr. William “Dollar” Young, Jr is an accomplished strategist and technical leader with 31 years in the United States Air Force. His last Air Force position was as the initial commander of the Air Force’s newest operational organization, a first-of-its-kind wing tasked to deliver Electromagnetic Spectrum capabilities to all Air Force weapon systems and platforms via “missionware” applications, mission data, advanced networking and Electromagnetic Warfare Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning algorithms.

Dr. Young is the creator of System-Theoretic Process Analysis for Security (STPA-Sec). STPA-Sec is the security analysis framework used to help secure many of America’s most complex new weapon systems. Dr. Young is a former consultant for MIT Lincoln Laboratory where he worked on new Security Engineering Analysis methods for the lab’s Cyber System Assessments Group. He is an Associate Research Professor at Syracuse University in the Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Dept. In this role, he is currently developing a new methodology for securing Internet of Things devices. Dr. Young previously served as the Chief Strategist for the Commander of the Air Force Air Education & Training Command.

Dr. Young earned his PhD at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) in 2016 in Systems Engineering with an emphasis in Secure Systems Engineering. He has four Master’s Degrees. Dr. Young was one of the initial graduates of the Air Force’s Grand Strategy Program. He has a Bachelor of Science in Engineering Science with an emphasis in Electrical and Aeronautical Engineering.

Alfred Berkeley
---------------

#### Advisor

A former president of NASDAQ. Was a Captain in the 438th Military Airlift Wing, and served as a Major in the USAF Reserve. He has testified before the Joint Committee on Economics of the US Congress, and before the House Science Committee, the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, and the House Committee on Homeland Security. Served on the International Advisory Council for the Monetary Authority of Singapore, and is currently on the Board of Visitors of the University of Maryland School of Medicine, and a Trustee of Hollins University. Al earned a B.A. from the University of Virginia, and received his M.B.A. from The Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania.
